saverr.com 2012-10-01

# Privacy Policy Meta Title

This privacy policy will come into effect for transactions after 20th November 2010.

Personal data, or personal information as it is sometimes called, is data that relates to or is capable of identifying a living person. Account holder privacy is very important to us and we do all we can to protect it.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know the type of information we may gather about you, how we may use it, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. 

## General Information

When you join Saverr your personal data will be collected, processed, stored and used by us and any other company within our group to, provide customer support, process payments we make to Account holders and for other purposes referred to in this Privacy Policy, the Saverr Account holder Agreement and any other agreements that Account holders may have with us.

Where we use "we" or "us" in our policy it refers to Lloyds Ventures the providers of the Saverr website and service.

When we refer to retailers, we mean sellers and suppliers of goods or services and other businesses that work with us (such as price- and quote-comparison services).

## The information we collect

**Personal data:** When you first sign-up with Saverr we ask for your name and email address. In addition, to help with security, we usually also capture your IP address.

Other personal information about you is then optional to provide, such as your date of birth, address, telephone number as well as household (such for instance, family-size) and lifestyle information (such as your personal interests).

**More personal data:** In some instances, we may also ask you for other sensitive personal information, for instance when obtaining and comparing insurance quotations from a retailer. This personal data may include information on your location (Address), physical or mental health or condition, allegations of criminality, criminal convictions, or sentences for convictions. You will be given the opportunity when providing the information to consent explicitly for the information to be shared with us, or a retailer (such as a provider of insurance quotations).

**Site usage:** When you visit Saverr we automatically log the information of your movement through the site. This could include how you got to the Saverr site, your IP address and what you look at while on the site.

For our in-store programme we use your registered card number to track your purchases to give you cashback.

We also use the services of an analytics provider to help us analyse this information. To do this we place a pixel on the pages of our site. The information collected allows us to improve the design of the site and does not include any personal information.

We will retain your personal data for as long as is permitted for legal, regulatory, taxation and fraud prevention purposes.

## Sharing of Information

When using Saverr you may make your personal data available to other businesses that work with us, including retailers, (such as price- and quote-comparison services). While these are businesses selected and trusted by Saverr it is your responsibility to ensure that you are happy to share your information with them (As explained in the More Personal Data comments above).

Your personal data may be disclosed if we, or an entity processing your data on our behalf are compelled to do so by law or receive a valid, legally compliant request by a law enforcement or governmental authority.

## Use of cookies

When your web browser accesses a specific web site such as ours, cookies (a type of small file) may, depending on your browser settings, be automatically stored on your computer's hard drive.

Cookies may be set by us, an affiliate network, or a retailer on both Saverr.com and retailer sites. When you go through to make a purchase on a retailer’s site it’s the cookie that gives us the information to track your cashback. Specifically it tells us which retailer’s site you’ve clicked through to and when. If you’ve made a purchase the cookie tells us the time you made it and the cashback amount. In some cases it may also record the product(s) (or type of product(s)) purchased and the value of the purchase.

## How we use cookie information

The cookie information allows us to calculate and allocate you the correct amount of cashback for your purchase. It also allows us to present tailored offers to you when you’re on Saverr.

We also put all the cookie information together anonymously (so your identity and personal details are not accessible) and use it for internal management purposes. We may share this information with current or prospective retailers as it really helps in negotiating better cashback rates. This will always be done at an aggregate level and no personal data will ever be shared.

## Managing your cookies

You can find out how to manage and remove cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies).

**If however you set your browser to reject cookies you may not be able to use certain aspects of Saverr and will not be able to earn cashback since theres no way for us to track the transaction.**

## Security

We’re committed to protecting your personal information. All information that you provide to us is stored on secure servers and access to this database is restricted internally. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we use reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

Access to your Saverr account is password-protected for your privacy and security. While we do our best to protect your personal information you also must protect yourself. What does this mean?

  * Keep your password or other access information secret.
  * Ensure no-one else uses Saverr while your machine is "signed in" to the Saverr site.
  * Make sure you sign out from your Saverr Account when not using it.

## Editing your account and mailing settings

We like to keep in touch with our Account holders so after you have signed up to Saverr we’ll send you information about products or services provided by us or our partners that we think will be of interest to you.

Of course we know lots of emails can be annoying so we try to keep ours to a minimum. However, if you feel you’re getting too many or would like more you can change the settings in your account at any time. Each communication gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving similar future communications. You can review, change or correct your identity and email address information by signing into your Saverr Account and going to the settings tab.

Please note there are some communications that are an integral part of the Saverr service and cannot be opted-out of. This covers, amongst other things, changes to our service and your actual or potential transactions with retailers i.e. Automated system generated messages

## Privacy Policies for other sites

While we promote lots of great offers and deals at Saverr, the majority of the time you’ll make your actual purchase on the site of a retailer. Each retailer will have its own independent practices concerning users’ privacy. You should check their privacy terms to make sure you are happy with them.

## Changes to this privacy statement

This policy is correct as of 08/11/2010. Any material changes to it will be announced on the Saverr site.

## Payout Terms

We are what is popularly referred to as a Marketplace. We offer a platform to retailers to promote their goods and similarly for the end customers to get the best out of their transaction. We generally pay our users as soon as the concerned merchant pays us for the transaction. This date range maybe somewhere between 30 to 60 days. All payouts done will be via **cheque** after you've confirmed your details. Also note that you are required by law to be 18 years or over in age to avail of the Cashback. In case of minors we will need to

## Your Obligations

Please note that once you've carried out a successful transaction on the website. You will need to wait for a period of 30-60 days for the cashback. We request this time frame because the payouts on part of the merchants happen within this time frame. You may need to provide additional data such as a recent photograph or a scanned copy of your PAN card in order to receive the cashback. Also note that you are obligated to notify us about the transaction and provide details pertinent to it should the need arise. This is needed by us in order to confirm whether a genuine transaction has ocurred and to make timely payments.
